priceviewer.com 2019-06-23

# None

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

## Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google's own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, priceviewer.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers. 

## Collection of Personal Information

When visiting priceviewer.com, the following information is collected: Internet Protocol (IP) address of computer being used; web pages requested; referring web page; browser used; browser language; date and time; statistics identifying particular IP addresses from which the Website is accessed.

## Use of Collected Information

The aggregated, anonymized data is periodically transmitted to external services to help us improve the Website and service. We currently use Google Analytics (traffic analysis, SEO optimization). Feel free to check out Google’s own [Privacy Policies](https://policies.google.com/privacy) to find out more. Other than this, we will not use the information that we collected for any commercial use.

## Affiliate Marketing

Certain contents and links that appear on this site come from affiliate networks such as, Commission Junction, Rakuten, eBay Partener Network, etc.. When you buy a product through this site, the affiliate networks pay us a percentage of each sale. This does not impact your price in any way, and helps us to keep the site online. 

## Changes to this Privacy Statement

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted. 

If you have any question or concern, please write to support@priceviewer.com.
